## Ajithkumar E, Full Stack Developer

8300048002, ea jith kumar 128@gmail.com

LINKS	Github, Portfolio, LinkedIN			
PROFILE	Ambitious problem-solving full stack web developer who is continually boosting a powerful set of technolog skills. I have 3+ years of experience in full stack development and have experience in working in AWS integratide deployment and docker.			
EMPLOYMENT HISTORY				
Apr 2021 — 2019	Full Stack Developer, Intellect Design Arena			Chennai
	Product Intelligent Data Extraction			
	<ul> <li>Designed an Annotation tool for PDF documents that helped in precisely extracting data from millions of insurance applications.</li> <li>Developed a commendable tool in detecting table structures in images and PDF documents.</li> <li>Developed a web UI for an Aadhaar Masking project.</li> <li>Worked in large scale data migration from Relational database to AWS S3 Buckets.</li> <li>Awarded for efficiently maintaining themes and configurations for multiple clients.</li> <li>Have experience in developing APIs in Node.js and Python.</li> </ul>			
Jul 2017 — Mar 2019	Software Engineer, Sopra Steria			Chennai
	Retail Application			
	<ul> <li>Designed a dashboard using React.js that helps business team in analyzing the every day sales report.</li> <li>Awarded for automating daily tasks.</li> <li>Created a tool that helps to keep track of the store closures.</li> </ul>			
EDUCATION				
Aug 2013 — Apr 2017	B.Teach IT, Karpagam College of Engineering Coimbatore			
	CGPA - 8.1			
SKILLS	JavaScript	Experienced	MongoDb	Experienced
	Vue.js	Expert	Websockets	Skillful
	React.js	Skillful	Docker	Skillful
	Node.js	Skillful	Github	Skillful
	Flask	Skillful	Python	Skillful
INTERNSHIPS				
Jul 2016 — Mar 2017	Associate Engineer, Informatica Bengalur			
	Product - ILM Data Archive			
	<ul> <li>Worked closely with customers to efficiently resolve issues.</li> <li>Got experience in working with multiple server environments and databases.</li> <li>Performed root cause analysis and general troubleshooting.</li> </ul>			
COURSES				
Jan 2018 — Apr 2018	Web developer bootCamp, Udemy			
Jul 2018 — Jan 2019	Full stack developer nanodegre, Udacity			